Hello
مرحبا
welcome to our first lesson in English listening practice.
مرحبا بكم في أول درس لنا في ممارسة الاستماع باللغة الإنجليزية.
Let's start today's lesson.
لنبدأ درس اليوم.
This lesson is very useful.
هذا الدرس مفيد جدا.
We're going to use important English phrases for
سنستخدم عبارات إنجليزية مهمة ل
the airport.
المطار.
Traveling can be stressful.
السفر يمكن أن يكون مرهقا.
I understand that.
أنا أفهم ذلك.
But if you know the common questions and phrases
ولكن إذا كنت تعرف الأسئلة والعبارات الشائعة
people use at the airport, and
الناس يستخدمون في المطار، و
if you know what to listen for, your trip
إذا كنت تعرف ما الذي تستمع إليه، فهو رحلتك
will feel much easier and less stressful.
سأشعر براحة أكبر وأقل توترا.
In this video, I will guide you.
في هذا الفيديو، سأرشدك.
I will speak slowly and clearly.
سأتحدث ببطء ووضوح.
Please listen carefully.
أرجو الاستماع جيدا.
If you want, you can repeat after me.
إذا أردت، يمكنك التكرار بعدي.
This will help improve both your listening skills
هذا سيساعد في تحسين مهارات الاستماع لديكم
and speaking skills.
ومهارات الكلام.
Are you ready?
هل أنت مستعد؟
Let's begin.
لنبدأ.